Uh, part of the reason why the government was reopened is also, of course, because the holidays are coming up and they want you to spend money. And I would say that unless you're spending money to buy food for people who don't have money, I would challenge y'all to consider figuring out how to celebrate the way you do.
I mean, I don't know why you celebrate Thanksgiving anyway, but nonetheless, consider challenging yourselves to make a gathering happen with like the normal amount of groceries you purchase. Potluck it or just do something other than.
Have sandwiches, you know, maybe have cereal, you know, maybe it's not a gathering to eat at all since that's at this point completely disregarding the actual massacres that took place of the First Nations people.
But maybe it's just getting together to figure out how to resist. Maybe it's getting together to play board games.
But ideally, it would be getting together to not spend in order to suspend the expansion of capitalist dollars into frameworks that are working to end us.
I can only imagine how I sound to some of y'all to the folks still in the Matrix.
I know I must sound like just the crazy lady in the too big coat, but they be knowing.
They be knowing.
Listen to your people.
Billionaire.